Guide to the Archives Union File Part 2, Section 1: Boxes 1-65 1872-1976
Archives Union File Part 2, Section 1: Boxes 1-65
- Coast Seamen's Journal, 1904; Publication (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Item 6: Coast Seamen's Journal, 1904; Publication (Box 8, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.17:no.32, whole no.864 (1904: May 4)
  - Item 7: Coast Seamen's Journal, 1904; Publication (Box 8, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.17:no.33, whole no.865 (1904: May 11)
  - Item 8: Coast Seamen's Journal, 1904; Publication (Box 8, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.17:no.34, whole no.866 (1904: May 18)
  - Item 9: Coast Seamen's Journal, 1904; Publication (Box 8, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.17:no.35, whole no.867 (1904: May 25)
  - Item 10: Coast Seamen's Journal, 1904; Publication (Box 8, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.17:no.36, whole no.868 (1904: June 1)
  - Item 11: Coast Seamen's Journal, 1904; Publication (Box 8, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.17:no.37, whole no.869 (1904: June 8)
  - Item 12: Coast Seamen's Journal, 1904; Publication (Box 8, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.17:no.38, whole no.870 (1904: June 15)
  - Item 13: Coast Seamen's Journal, 1904; Publication (Box 8, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.17:no.39, whole no.871 (1904: June 22)
  - Item 14: Coast Seamen's Journal, 1904; Publication (Box 8, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.17:no.40, whole no.872 (1904: June 29)
  - Item 15: Coast Seamen's Journal, 1904; Publication (Box 8, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.17:no.41, whole no.873 (1904: July 6)
  - Item 16: Coast Seamen's Journal, 1904; Publication (Box 8, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.17:no.42, whole no.874 (1904: July 13)
  - Item 17: Coast Seamen's Journal, 1904; Publication (Box 8, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.17:no.43, whole no.875 (1904: July 20)
  - Item 18: Coast Seamen's Journal, 1904; Publication (Box 8, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.17:no.44, whole no.876 (1904: July 27)
  - Item 19: Coast Seamen's Journal, 1904; Publication (Box 8, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.17:no.45, whole no.877 (1904: Aug. 3)
  - Item 20: Coast Seamen's Journal, 1904; Publication (Box 8, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.17:no.46, whole no.878 (1904: Aug. 10)
  - Item 21: Coast Seamen's Journal, 1904; Publication (Box 8, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.17:no.47, whole no.879 (1904: Aug. 17)
  - Item 22: Coast Seamen's Journal, 1904; Publication (Box 8, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.17:no.48, whole no.880 (1904: Aug. 24)
  - Item 23: Coast Seamen's Journal, 1904; Publication (Box 8, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.17:no.49, whole no.881 (1904: Aug. 31)
  - Item 24: Coast Seamen's Journal, 1904; Publication (Box 8, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.17:no.50, whole no.882 (1904: Sept. 7)
  - Item 25: Coast Seamen's Journal, 1904; Publication (Box 8, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.17:no.51, whole no.883 (1904: Sept. 14)
  - Item 26: Coast Seamen's Journal, 1904; Publication (Box 8, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.17:no.52, whole no.884 (1904: Sept. 21)
- Coast Seamen's Journal, 1904-1905 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Coast Seamen's Journal, 1904-1905 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.18 Index: September 29, 1904 - September 20, 1905.
  - Item 2: Coast Seamen's Journal, 1904; Publication (Box 8, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.18:no.1, whole no.885 (1904: Sept. 28)
  - Item 3: Coast Seamen's Journal, 1904; Publication (Box 8, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.18:no.2, whole no.886 (1904: Oct. 5)
  - Item 4: Coast Seamen's Journal, 1904; Publication (Box 8, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.18:no.3, whole no.887 (1904: Oct. 12)
  - Item 5: Coast Seamen's Journal, 1904; Publication (Box 8, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.18:no.4, whole no.888 (1904: Oct. 19)
  - Item 6: Coast Seamen's Journal, 1904; Publication (Box 8, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.18:no.5, whole no.889 (1904: Oct. 26)
  - Item 7: Coast Seamen's Journal, 1904; Publication (Box 8, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.18:no.6, whole no.890 (1904: Nov. 2)
  - Item 8: Coast Seamen's Journal, 1904; Publication (Box 8, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.18:no.7, whole no.891 (1904: Nov. 9)
  - Item 9: Coast Seamen's Journal, 1904; Publication (Box 8, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.18:no.8, whole no.892 (1904: Nov. 16)
  - Item 10: Coast Seamen's Journal, 1904; Publication (Box 8, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.18:no.9, whole no.893 (1904: Nov. 23)
  - Item 11: Coast Seamen's Journal, 1904; Publication (Box 8, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.18:no.10, whole no.894 (1904: Nov. 30)
  - Item 12: Coast Seamen's Journal, 1904; Publication (Box 8, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.18:no.11, whole no.895 (1904: Dec. 7)
  - Item 13: Coast Seamen's Journal, 1904; Publication (Box 8, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.18:no.12, whole no.896 (1904: Dec. 14)
  - Item 14: Coast Seamen's Journal, 1904; Publication (Box 8, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.18:no.13, whole no.897 (1904: Dec. 21)
  - Item 15: Coast Seamen's Journal, 1904; Publication (Box 8, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.18:no.14, whole no.898 (1904: Dec. 28)
  - Item 16: Coast Seamen's Journal, 1905; Publication (Box 8, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.18:no.15, whole no.899 (1905: Jan. 4)
  - Item 17: Coast Seamen's Journal, 1905; Publication (Box 8, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.18:no.16, whole no.900 (1905: Jan. 11)
  - Item 18: Coast Seamen's Journal, 1905; Publication (Box 8, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.18:no.17, whole no.901 (1905: Jan. 18)
  - Item 19: Coast Seamen's Journal, 1905; Publication (Box 8, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.18:no.18, whole no.902 (1905: Jan. 25)
  - Item 20: Coast Seamen's Journal, 1905; Publication (Box 8, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.18:no.19, whole no.903 (1905: Feb. 1)
  - Item 21: Coast Seamen's Journal, 1905; Publication (Box 8, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.18:no.20, whole no.904 (1905: Feb. 8)
  - Item 22: Coast Seamen's Journal, 1905; Publication (Box 8, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.18:no.21, whole no.905 (1905: Feb. 15)
  - Item 23: Coast Seamen's Journal, 1905; Publication (Box 8, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.18:no.22, whole no.906 (1905: Feb. 22)
  - Item 24: Coast Seamen's Journal, 1905; Publication (Box 8, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.18:no.23, whole no.907 (1905: Mar. 1)
  - Item 25: Coast Seamen's Journal, 1905; Publication (Box 8, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.18:no.24, whole no.908 (1905: Mar. 8)
  - Item 26: Coast Seamen's Journal, 1905; Publication (Box 8, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.18:no.25, whole no.909 (1905: Mar. 15)
  - Item 27: Coast Seamen's Journal, 1905; Publication (Box 8, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.18:no.26, whole no.910 (1905: Mar. 22)
- Coast Seamen's Journal, 1905; Publication (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Coast Seamen's Journal, 1905; Publication (Box 9, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.18:no.27, whole no.911 (1905: Mar. 29)
  - Item 2: Coast Seamen's Journal, 1905; Publication (Box 9, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.18:no.28, whole no.912 (1905: Apr. 5)
  - Item 3: Coast Seamen's Journal, 1905; Publication (Box 9, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.18:no.29, whole no.913 (1905: Apr. 12)
  - Item 4: Coast Seamen's Journal, 1905; Publication (Box 9, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.18:no.30, whole no.914 (1905: Apr. 19)
  - Item 5: Coast Seamen's Journal, 1905; Publication (Box 9, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.18:no.31, whole no.915 (1905: Apr. 26)
  - Item 6: Coast Seamen's Journal, 1905; Publication (Box 9, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.18:no.32, whole no.916 (1905: May 3)
  - Item 7: Coast Seamen's Journal, 1905; Publication (Box 9, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.18:no.33, whole no.917 (1905: May 10)
  - Item 8: Coast Seamen's Journal, 1905; Publication (Box 9, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.18:no.34, whole no.918 (1905: May 17)
  - Item 9: Coast Seamen's Journal, 1905; Publication (Box 9, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.18:no.35, whole no.919 (1905: May 24)
  - Item 10: Coast Seamen's Journal, 1905; Publication (Box 9, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.18:no.36, whole no.920 (1905: May 31)
  - Item 11: Coast Seamen's Journal, 1905; Publication (Box 9, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.18:no.37, whole no.921 (1905: June 7)
  - Item 12: Coast Seamen's Journal, 1905; Publication (Box 9, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.18:no.38, whole no.922 (1905: June 14)
  - Item 13: Coast Seamen's Journal, 1905; Publication (Box 9, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.18:no.39, whole no.923 (1905: June 21)
  - Item 14: Coast Seamen's Journal, 1905; Publication (Box 9, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.18:no.40, whole no.924 (1905: June 28)
  - Item 15: Coast Seamen's Journal, 1905; Publication (Box 9, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.18:no.41, whole no.925 (1905: July 5)
  - Item 16: Coast Seamen's Journal, 1905; Publication (Box 9, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.18:no.42, whole no.926 (1905: July 12)
  - Item 17: Coast Seamen's Journal, 1905; Publication (Box 9, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.18:no.43, whole no.927 (1905: July 19)
  - Item 18: Coast Seamen's Journal, 1905; Publication (Box 9, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.18:no.44, whole no.928 (1905: July 26)
  - Item 19: Coast Seamen's Journal, 1905; Publication (Box 9, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.18:no.45, whole no.929 (1905: Aug. 2)
  - Item 20: Coast Seamen's Journal, 1905; Publication (Box 9, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.18:no.46, whole no.930 (1905: Aug. 9)
  - Item 21: Coast Seamen's Journal, 1905; Publication (Box 9, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.18:no.47, whole no.931 (1905: Aug. 16)
  - Item 22: Coast Seamen's Journal, 1905; Publication (Box 9, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.18:no.48, whole no.932 (1905: Aug. 23)
  - Item 23: Coast Seamen's Journal, 1905; Publication (Box 9, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.18:no.49, whole no.933 (1905: Aug. 30)
  - Item 24: Coast Seamen's Journal, 1905; Publication (Box 9, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.18:no.50, whole no.934 (1905: Sept. 6)
  - Item 25: Coast Seamen's Journal, 1905; Publication (Box 9, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.18:no.51, whole no.935 (1905: Sept. 13)
  - Item 26: Coast Seamen's Journal, 1905; Publication (Box 9, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.18:no.52, whole no.936 (1905: Sept. 20)
- Coast Seamen's Journal, 1905-1906 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Coast Seamen's Journal, 1905; Publication (Box 9, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.19:no.1, whole no.937 (1905: Sept. 27)
  - Item 2: Coast Seamen's Journal, 1905; Publication (Box 9, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.19:no.2, whole no.938 (1905: Oct. 4)
  - Item 3: Coast Seamen's Journal, 1905; Publication (Box 9, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.19:no.3, whole no.939 (1905: Oct. 11)
  - Item 4: Coast Seamen's Journal, 1905; Publication (Box 9, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.19:no.4, whole no.940 (1905: Oct. 18)
  - Item 5: Coast Seamen's Journal, 1905; Publication (Box 9, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.19:no.5, whole no.941 (1905: Oct. 25)
  - Item 6: Coast Seamen's Journal, 1905; Publication (Box 9, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.19:no.6, whole no.942 (1905: Nov. 1)
  - Item 7: Coast Seamen's Journal, 1905; Publication (Box 9, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.19:no.7, whole no.943 (1905: Nov. 8)
  - Item 8: Coast Seamen's Journal, 1905; Publication (Box 9, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.19:no.8, whole no.944 (1905: Nov. 15)
  - Item 9: Coast Seamen's Journal, 1905; Publication (Box 9, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.19:no.9, whole no.945 (1905: Nov. 22)
  - Item 10: Coast Seamen's Journal, 1905; Publication (Box 9, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.19:no.10, whole no.946 (1905: Nov. 29)
  - Item 11: Coast Seamen's Journal, 1905; Publication (Box 9, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.19:no.11, whole no.947 (1905: Dec. 6)
  - Item 12: Coast Seamen's Journal, 1905; Publication (Box 9, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.19:no.12, whole no.948 (1905: Dec. 13)
  - Item 13: Coast Seamen's Journal, 1905; Publication (Box 9, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.19:no.13, whole no.949 (1905: Dec. 20)
  - Item 14: Coast Seamen's Journal, 1905; Publication (Box 9, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.19:no.14, whole no.950 (1905: Dec. 27)
  - Item 15: Coast Seamen's Journal, 1906; Publication (Box 9, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.19:no.15, whole no.951 (1906: Jan. 3)
  - Item 16: Coast Seamen's Journal, 1906; Publication (Box 9, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.19:no.16, whole no.952 (1906: Jan. 10)
  - Item 17: Coast Seamen's Journal, 1906; Publication (Box 9, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.19:no.17, whole no.953 (1906: Jan. 17)
  - Item 18: Coast Seamen's Journal, 1906; Publication (Box 9, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.19:no.18, whole no.954 (1906: Jan. 24)
  - Item 19: Coast Seamen's Journal, 1906; Publication (Box 9, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.19:no.19, whole no.955 (1906: Jan. 31)
  - Item 20: Coast Seamen's Journal, 1906; Publication (Box 9, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.19:no.20, whole no.956 (1906: Feb. 7)
  - Item 21: Coast Seamen's Journal, 1906; Publication (Box 9, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.19:no.21, whole no.957 (1906: Feb. 14)
  - Item 22: Coast Seamen's Journal, 1906; Publication (Box 9, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.19:no.22, whole no.958 (1906: Feb. 21)
  - Item 23: Coast Seamen's Journal, 1906; Publication (Box 9, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.19:no.23, whole no.959 (1906: Feb. 28)
  - Item 24: Coast Seamen's Journal, 1906; Publication (Box 9, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.19:no.24, whole no.960 (1906: Mar. 7)
  - Item 25: Coast Seamen's Journal, 1906; Publication (Box 9, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.19:no.25, whole no.961 (1906: Mar. 14)
  - Item 26: Coast Seamen's Journal, 1906; Publication (Box 9, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.19:no.26, whole no.962 (1906: Mar. 21)
- Coast Seamen's Journal, 1906; Publication (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Coast Seamen's Journal, 1906; Publication (Box 9, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.19:no.27, whole no.963 (1906: Mar. 28)
  - Item 2: Coast Seamen's Journal, 1906; Publication (Box 9, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.19:no.28, whole no.964 (1906: Apr. 4)
  - Item 3: Coast Seamen's Journal, 1906; Publication (Box 9, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.19:no.29, whole no.965 (1906: Apr. 11)
  - Item 4: Coast Seamen's Journal, 1906; Publication (Box 9, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.19:no.30, whole no.966 (1906: Apr. 18)
  - Item 5: Coast Seamen's Journal, 1906; Publication (Box 9, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.19:no.31, whole no.967 (1906: Apr. 25)
  - Item 6: Coast Seamen's Journal, 1906; Publication (Box 9, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.19:no.32, whole no.968 (1906: May 2)
  - Item 7: Coast Seamen's Journal, 1906; Publication (Box 9, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.19:no.33, whole no.969 (1906: May 9)
  - Item 8: Coast Seamen's Journal, 1906; Publication (Box 9, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.19:no.34, whole no.970 (1906: May 16)
  - Item 9: Coast Seamen's Journal, 1906; Publication (Box 9, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.19:no.35, whole no.971 (1906: May 23)
  - Item 10: Coast Seamen's Journal, 1906; Publication (Box 9, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.19:no.36, whole no.972 (1906: May 30)
  - Item 11: Coast Seamen's Journal, 1906; Publication (Box 9, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.19:no.37, whole no.973 (1906: June 6)
  - Item 12: Coast Seamen's Journal, 1906; Publication (Box 9, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.19:no.38, whole no.974 (1906: June 13)
  - Item 13: Coast Seamen's Journal, 1906; Publication (Box 9, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.19:no.39, whole no.975 (1906: June 20)
  - Item 14: Coast Seamen's Journal, 1906; Publication (Box 9, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.19:no.40, whole no.976 (1906: June 27)
  - Item 15: Coast Seamen's Journal, 1906; Publication (Box 9, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.19:no.41, whole no.977 (1906: July 4)
  - Item 16: Coast Seamen's Journal, 1906; Publication (Box 9, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.19:no.42, whole no.978 (1906: July 11)
  - Item 17: Coast Seamen's Journal, 1906; Publication (Box 9, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.19:no.42, whole no.978 (1906: July 11). Copy 2.
  - Item 18: Coast Seamen's Journal, 1906; Publication (Box 9, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.19:no.43, whole no.979 (1906: July 18)
  - Item 19: Coast Seamen's Journal, 1906; Publication (Box 9, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.19:no.44, whole no.980 (1906: July 25)
  - Item 20: Coast Seamen's Journal, 1906; Publication (Box 9, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.19:no.45, whole no.981 (1906: Aug. 1)
  - Item 21: Coast Seamen's Journal, 1906; Publication (Box 9, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.19:no.46, whole no.982 (1906: Aug. 8)
  - Item 22: Coast Seamen's Journal, 1906; Publication (Box 9, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.19:no.47, whole no.983 (1906: Aug. 15)
  - Item 23: Coast Seamen's Journal, 1906; Publication (Box 9, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.19:no.48, whole no.984 (1906: Aug. 22)
  - Item 24: Coast Seamen's Journal, 1906; Publication (Box 9, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.19:no.49, whole no.985 (1906: Aug. 29)
  - Item 25: Coast Seamen's Journal, 1906; Publication (Box 9, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.19:no.50, whole no.986 (1906: Sept. 5)
  - Item 26: Coast Seamen's Journal, 1906; Publication (Box 9, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.19:no.51, whole no.987 (1906: Sept. 12)
  - Item 27: Coast Seamen's Journal, 1906; Publication (Box 9, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.19:no.52, whole no.988 (1906: Sept. 19)
- Coast Seamen's Journal, 1906-1907 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Coast Seamen's Journal, 1906; Publication (Box 10, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.20:no.1, whole no.989 (1906: Sept. 26)
  - Item 2: Coast Seamen's Journal, 1906; Publication (Box 10, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.20:no.2, whole no.990 (1906: Oct. 3)
  - Item 3: Coast Seamen's Journal, 1906; Publication (Box 10, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.20:no.3, whole no.991 (1906: Oct. 10)
  - Item 4: Coast Seamen's Journal, 1906; Publication (Box 10, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.20:no.4, whole no.992 (1906: Oct. 17)
  - Item 5: Coast Seamen's Journal, 1906; Publication (Box 10, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.20:no.5, whole no.993 (1906: Oct. 24)
  - Item 6: Coast Seamen's Journal, 1906; Publication (Box 10, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.20:no.6, whole no.994 (1906: Oct. 31)
  - Item 7: Coast Seamen's Journal, 1906; Publication (Box 10, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.20:no.7, whole no.995 (1906: Nov. 7)
  - Item 8: Coast Seamen's Journal, 1906; Publication (Box 10, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.20:no.8, whole no.996 (1906: Nov. 14)
  - Item 9: Coast Seamen's Journal, 1906; Publication (Box 10, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.20:no.9, whole no.997 (1906: Nov. 21)
  - Item 10: Coast Seamen's Journal, 1906; Publication (Box 10, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.20:no.10, whole no.998 (1906: Nov. 28)
  - Item 11: Coast Seamen's Journal, 1906; Publication (Box 10, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.20:no.11, whole no.999 (1906: Dec. 5)
  - Item 12: Coast Seamen's Journal, 1906; Publication (Box 10, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.20:no.12, whole no.1000 (1906: Dec. 12)
  - Item 13: Coast Seamen's Journal, 1906; Publication (Box 10, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.20:no.13, whole no.1001 (1906: Dec. 19)
  - Item 14: Coast Seamen's Journal, 1906; Publication (Box 10, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.20:no.14, whole no.1002 (1906: Dec. 26)
  - Item 15: Coast Seamen's Journal, 1907; Publication (Box 10, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.20:no.15, whole no.1003 (1907: Jan. 2)
  - Item 16: Coast Seamen's Journal, 1907; Publication (Box 10, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.20:no.16, whole no.1004 (1907: Jan. 9)
  - Item 17: Coast Seamen's Journal, 1907; Publication (Box 10, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.20:no.17, whole no.1005 (1907: Jan. 16)
  - Item 18: Coast Seamen's Journal, 1907; Publication (Box 10, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.20:no.18, whole no.1006 (1907: Jan. 23)
  - Item 19: Coast Seamen's Journal, 1907; Publication (Box 10, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.20:no.19, whole no.1007 (1907: Jan. 30)
  - Item 20: Coast Seamen's Journal, 1907; Publication (Box 10, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.20:no.20, whole no.1008 (1907: Feb. 6)
  - Item 21: Coast Seamen's Journal, 1907; Publication (Box 10, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.20:no.21, whole no.1009 (1907: Feb. 13)
  - Item 22: Coast Seamen's Journal, 1907; Publication (Box 10, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.20:no.22, whole no.1010 (1907: Feb. 20)
  - Item 23: Coast Seamen's Journal, 1907; Publication (Box 10, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.20:no.23, whole no.1011 (1907: Feb. 27)
  - Item 24: Coast Seamen's Journal, 1907; Publication (Box 10, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.20:no.24, whole no.1012 (1907: Mar. 6)
  - Item 25: Coast Seamen's Journal, 1907; Publication (Box 10, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.20:no.25, whole no.1013 (1907: Mar. 13)
  - Item 26: Coast Seamen's Journal, 1907; Publication (Box 10, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.20:no.26, whole no.1014 (1907: Mar. 20)
- Coast Seamen's Journal, 1907; Publication (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Coast Seamen's Journal, 1907; Publication (Box 10, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.20:no.27, whole no.1015 (1907: Mar. 27)
  - Item 2: Coast Seamen's Journal, 1907; Publication (Box 10, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.20:no.28, whole no.1016 (1907: Apr. 3)
  - Item 3: Coast Seamen's Journal, 1907; Publication (Box 10, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.20:no.29, whole no.1017 (1907: Apr. 10)
  - Item 4: Coast Seamen's Journal, 1907; Publication (Box 10, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.20:no.30, whole no.1018 (1907: Apr. 17)
  - Item 5: Coast Seamen's Journal, 1907; Publication (Box 10, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.20:no.31, whole no.1019 (1907: Apr. 24)
  - Item 6: Coast Seamen's Journal, 1907; Publication (Box 10, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.20:no.32, whole no.1020 (1907: May 1)
  - Item 7: Coast Seamen's Journal, 1907; Publication (Box 10, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.20:no.33, whole no.1021 (1907: May 8)
  - Item 8: Coast Seamen's Journal, 1907; Publication (Box 10, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.20:no.34, whole no.1022 (1907: May 15)
  - Item 9: Coast Seamen's Journal, 1907; Publication (Box 10, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.20:no.35, whole no.1023 (1907: May 22)
  - Item 10: Coast Seamen's Journal, 1907; Publication (Box 10, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.20:no.36, whole no.1024 (1907: May 19)
  - Item 11: Coast Seamen's Journal, 1907; Publication (Box 10, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.20:no.37, whole no.1025 (1907: June 5)
  - Item 12: Coast Seamen's Journal, 1907; Publication (Box 10, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.20:no.38, whole no.1026 (1907: June 12)
  - Item 13: Coast Seamen's Journal, 1907; Publication (Box 10, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.20:no.39, whole no.1027 (1907: June 19)
  - Item 14: Coast Seamen's Journal, 1907; Publication (Box 10, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.20:no.40, whole no.1028 (1907: June 26)
  - Item 15: Coast Seamen's Journal, 1907; Publication (Box 10, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.20:no.41, whole no.1029 (1907: July 3)
  - Item 16: Coast Seamen's Journal, 1907; Publication (Box 10, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.20:no.42, whole no.1030 (1907: July 10)
  - Item 17: Coast Seamen's Journal, 1907; Publication (Box 10, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.20:no.43, whole no.1031 (1907: July 17)
  - Item 18: Coast Seamen's Journal, 1907; Publication (Box 10, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.20:no.44, whole no.1032 (1907: July 24)
  - Item 19: Coast Seamen's Journal, 1907; Publication (Box 10, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.20:no.45, whole no.1033 (1907: July 31)
  - Item 20: Coast Seamen's Journal, 1907; Publication (Box 10, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.20:no.46, whole no.1034 (1907: Aug. 7)
  - Item 21: Coast Seamen's Journal, 1907; Publication (Box 10, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.20:no.47, whole no.1035 (1907: Aug. 14)
  - Item 22: Coast Seamen's Journal, 1907; Publication (Box 10, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.20:no.48, whole no.1036 (1907: Aug. 21)
  - Item 23: Coast Seamen's Journal, 1907; Publication (Box 10, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.20:no.49, whole no.1037 (1907: Aug. 28)
  - Item 24: Coast Seamen's Journal, 1907; Publication (Box 10, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.20:no.50, whole no.1038 (1907: Sept. 4)
  - Item 25: Coast Seamen's Journal, 1907; Publication (Box 10, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.20:no.51, whole no.1039 (1907: Sept. 11)
  - Item 26: Coast Seamen's Journal, 1907; Publication (Box 10, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.20:no.52, whole no.1040 (1907: Sept. 18)
- Coast Seamen's Journal, 1907-1908 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Coast Seamen's Journal, 1907; Publication (Box 10, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.21:no.1, whole no.1041 (1907: Sept. 25)
  - Item 2: Coast Seamen's Journal, 1907; Publication (Box 10, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.21:no.2, whole no.1042 (1907: Oct. 2)
  - Item 3: Coast Seamen's Journal, 1907; Publication (Box 10, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.21:no.3, whole no.1043 (1907: Oct. 9)
  - Item 4: Coast Seamen's Journal, 1907; Publication (Box 10, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.21:no.4, whole no.1044 (1907: Oct. 16)
  - Item 5: Coast Seamen's Journal, 1907; Publication (Box 10, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.21:no.5, whole no.1045 (1907: Oct. 23)
  - Item 6: Coast Seamen's Journal, 1907; Publication (Box 10, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.21:no.6, whole no.1046 (1907: Oct. 30)
  - Item 7: Coast Seamen's Journal, 1907; Publication (Box 10, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.21:no.7, whole no.1047 (1907: Nov. 6)
  - Item 8: Coast Seamen's Journal, 1907; Publication (Box 10, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.21:no.8, whole no.1048 (1907: Nov. 13)